Ihza Ahmad Abror Amrullah

Balikpapan, East Kalimantan • Github • LinkedIn • ihzaahmad0@gmail.com • +6281348078610

Summary

I am a graduate my degree in **informatics engineering** at Universitas Muhammadiyah Malang with 3.88 GPA. I am passionate and interested in field of **website programmer**. I have 3 years experience as a **website programmer** especially using **PHP** (**Laravel**) and **Nodejs** (**Express.js**) and I am success build about **22 websites**. I used to using **ORM** (**eloquent**) to communicate with **database** like **MySQL** and deploying the system to **linux** environment. I can develop responsive and high-performance websites. I can also develop **REST API** applications. I'm used to using **version control** like **git**. I also ensure to code according to **standards** and **best practices** to facilitate future maintenance and to enhance system security.

Work Experience



Software Developer

PT Nindya Karya

October 2022 - Present

- 1. Successfully developed and managed 3 websites:
 - a. QHSE (Quality Health & Safety Environment)

October 2022 - Present

- A website used for recording employee working hours, workplace accidents, daily reports, and more.
- Successfully completed the project using Laravel, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, GitLab, and MySQL.

b. Inindya

January 2023 - Present

- A digital workplace website with Laravel, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, GitLab, and PostgreSQL.
- ii. Successfully created and managed the DMS (Document Management System)
- iii. Successfully created and managed the LENS (Legal Information System) module.

c. Corporate Website

August 2023

- i. Website company profile dan customer feedback.
- ii. Successfully created and managed the Customer Area module using **CodeIgniter**, **JavaScript**, **jQuery**, **AJAX**, **GitLab**, and **PostgreSQL**.



Full-Stack / Back-End Website Programmer

Universitas Muhammadiyah Malang

October 2021 - Present

- 1. Successfully built 3 internal campus ERP projects.
 - a. SIM-Lab Psikologi

July - August 2022

- i. Website used for recording assets at Lab Psikologi.
- ii. Successfully complete **3 modules**: transaction procurement, reports, and transaction submission in 1 months.
- iii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Javascript, Jquery, AJAX, and MySql.

b. SIMASET

December 2021 – February 2022

- i. Website used for recording assets at Universitas Muhammadiyah Malang.
- ii. Successfully complete **4 modules**: master, transaction procurement, reports, and transaction submission in 2 months.
- ii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Javascript, Jquery, AJAX, and MySql.

c. SIMKATMAWA

October - November 2021

- i. Website used to record student achievements.
- ii. Successfully complete **1 module**: transaction achievements in 1 month.
- iii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Javascript, Jquery, AJAX, and MySql.
- 2. Successfully built 2 new student management projects.

a. **KESI**

March - April 2022

 Website that is used to promote campus course programs specifically for prospective students.

- ii. Successfully complete **4 modules**: authentication, student registration, master, and course in 1 month.
- iii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, AJAX, and MySql (KESI).

b. COE

Mei – June 2022

- i. Website used for course management for students and prospective students.
- ii. Successfully complete **4 modules**: authentication, student registration, master, and proposal in 1 month.
- iii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, AJAX, and MySql (COE).



Full-Stack Website Programmer

Stand Studio Surabaya

July 2021 - September 2021

- 1. Successfully built 3 ERP client projects and tire management projects.
 - a. Masofindo

July 2021

- i. ERP website for Masofindo company.
- ii. Successfully complete 3 modules: transaction, reports, and master in 1 month.
- iii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, MySQL and Vue Js.

b. <u>idr.network</u>

July 2021

- i. Website to record the entry and exit of goods.
- ii. Successfully complete 2 modules: transaction, and reports in 1 month.
- iii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, MySQL and Vue Js.
- c. SDSB

August 2021

- i. Website for manage residential residents.
- ii. Successfully complete **2 modules**: transfers of funds, and reports in 1 month.
- iii. Successfully build the project using PHP, Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, MySQL and Vue Js.
- d. Tire management

September 2021

- i. Website for manage and record usage history of tires.
- ii. Successfully complete 1 module transaction tire in 1 month.
- Successfully build the project using PHP, Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, Ajax, MySQL and Vue Js.

Project Experience



Backend Programmer at E-Desa Project

CV. Unimasoft

July 2022 - Present

- 1. E-Desa is a system for record residents of a village. E-Desa have website and mobile application.
- 2. Successfully become the lead programmer.
- 3. Successfully complete 3 modules: authentication, resident, and family card.
- 4. Successfully develop the system using Laravel and MySQL (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Management Information System RSU UMM Project

Freelance

January 2022 - Present

- 1. Website for manage and record all data in RSU UMM.
- 2. Become the lead programmer.
- 3. Successfully complete **5 modules**: authentication, queue patient, vclaim, reports, and medical resume.
- 4. Successfully **bridging** with BPJS Kesehatan (github, website).
- 5. Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Websockets, MySQL, Ajax, and Jquery.



Fullstack Programmer at Management Information System RS Wava Kesamben Project Freelance

May - June 2021

- 1. Website for manage and record all data in RS Wava Kesamben Project.
- 2. Become the lead programmer.

- 3. Successfully complete **4 modules**: authentication, master doctor, master clinic, and services in 1 month.
- 4. Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Ajax, and MySQL (github, website).



Fullstack Programmer at Mentari Supermarkets Online Stores Project

Freelance - Mentari Supermarket Malang

March 2021

- 1. Online store website for online transaction, the user can buy some goods from Mentari Supermarkets.
- 2. Become the lead programmer.
- 3. Successfully complete **3 modules**: authentication, master product, and checkout product in 1 month.
- 4. Successfully develop the system using Laravel and Vue.Js with SPA architecture (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Animal Adoption Website Project

Internship - CV. Hummasoft Technology

January - February 2021

- 1. Social media website for sharing information about abandoned animal.
- Successfully complete 4 modules: authentication, post, comment, and link or dislike in 1 month.
- Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Ajax, Jquery, and MySQL (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Information Event Website Project

Freelance – Univeristas Brawijaya

December 2020

- 1. Website for publication of event information at Universitas Brawijaya.
- 2. Successfully complete 2 modules: authentication and event in 1 month.
- 3. Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Ajax, Jquery, and MySQL (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Project Information System Website in Sangen Village, Madiun Regency

Freelance

October 2020

- 1. Information system website used to generate online letters.
- 2. Successfully complete 1 module: generates letters in 1 month.
- 3. Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Ajax, Jquery, and MySQL (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Project Website Information System and Donation Of Ulil Abshar Orphanage

Freelance - Panti Asuhan Ulil Abshar Malang

August - September 2020

- 1. Information system website used to donation and profile of Ulil Abshar Orphanage.
- 2. Successfully complete 3 modules: authentication, blog, and donators in 2 months.
- Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Ajax, Jquery, and MySQL (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Project Website Generate Certificate LPKIPI

Freelance - LPKIPI

July 2020

- 1. Website for easily generate and verify certificate.
- 2. Successfully complete **3 modules**: authentication, generate certificate, and verify certificate in 1 month.
- Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Ajax, Jquery, and MySQL (github, website).



Fullstack Programmer at Informatics Labolatory Quality Management Information **System Project**

Lab Informatika UMM

April 2020

- 1. Facility and Resource Quality Assessment and Evaluation System Lab Informatika UMM.
- 2. Successfully complete 2 modules: Feedback Instructor, and Assistance in 1 month.
- 3. Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Ajax, Jquery, and MySQL (github, website).



Fullstack Programmer at Project Website Community Social Media

Internship - CV. Hummasoft Technology

February 2020

- 1. Social media website for the community to communicate with each other.
- 2. Successfully complete 3 modules: post, comment, and like or dislike in 1 month.
- 3. Successfully develop the system using CI, Javascript, Ajax, Jquery, and MySQL (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Project Website Pesantren Negeri Akhirat

Internship - PT. Exel Sistem Solusindo

January 2020

- 1. Company profile website for Pesantren Negeri Akhirat.
- 2. Successfully complete 6 modules: authentication, master, news, announcements, student, and teacher 1 month.
- 3. Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, and MySQL (github).



Fullstack Programmer at Project Informatics Laboratory Participant Recruitment System **UMM**

Lab Informatika UMM

August 2019

- 1. Website for registration and exam laboratory participant recruitment.
- 2. Successfully complete 2 modules: timeline and registration in 1 month.
- 3. Successfully develop the system using Laravel, Javascript, Jquery, and MySQL (github, website).

Education



Universitas Muhammadiyah Malang

Informatics Engineering [2017 – 2021] **GPA 3.88**



SMK Negeri 6 Balikpapan

Computer and Network Engineering [2013 – 2016]

Organization



Infotech - Lab Informatika UMM

2018 - 2020

Member and assistance laboratory

Honors & Awards



2nd best graduate of engineering faculty 2nd group at 2021



Achieve kaltim tuntas 2019 scholarship



Become fasilitor of event BDT dicoding 2020 (certificate)

Tools

• Visual Studio Code • Github • Gitlab • Postman • Insomnia • Chrome Developer Tools • FileZilla • PuTTY • Navicat • phpMyAdmin • chatgpt